

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a Web developer with 2 years of experience, studies of Web and Mobile Development, skills in javascript, React, CSS, HTML, Nodejs, PHP, Redux, MySQL and hobbies in Hiking, Kickboxing, Traveling. I have developed a strong work ethic and I am very motivated to learn new technologies and to keep up to date with current industry trends. I am a very positive person and I work well under pressure. I am also a very proactive person and I am always willing to take on new challenges.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5

CSS

**JAVASCRIPT** 

REACT

REDUX

**NODEJS** 

PHP

**EXPRESS** 

MySQL

### LANGUANGE

Norwegian Native English Proficient

Spanish Intermediate

French
Intermediate

# ANDREAS **GJERTSEN**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

- +41-76-526-93-42
- ★ kaliqani7@gmail.com
- Lausanne, Switzerland
- www.agkportofolio.com

## **EXPERIENCE**

2022-2022 ASSISTANT TEACHER FRONTEND PowerHouse, Lausanne 01.03.2022-01.11.2022

- Assisted web developers with coding and debugging web applications
- Tested web applications for functionality and user experience
- Wrote code to improve web application performance
- Provided support to web developers during web application launches

2021-2021 FRONTEND DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP

Redefine, Copenhaven Denmark 01.05.2022.-01.08.2022

- Provided website maintenance and enhancements
- Diagnosed and resolved defects and emergencies
- Worked on code fixes and code deployments
- Assisted in the creation of technical documentation
- Conducted research on new web technologies
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to improve the user experience

### **EDUCATION**

2021-2021 Web and Mobile Developer Fullstack

Wilde Code School, Barcelona 01.03.2021-01.08.2021

- Developed and designed user interfaces and experience for web application
- Learning HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React. Redux, Nodejs, Express, MySQl
- Working in Agile group creating five projects using best practices for frontend and back development